Jackie Martin Papers
Jackie Martin Papers
- Negatives and contacts
  - World War II War correspondent, 1944
    - 93rd sets up at Rogenette; Lt. Watts and Cols. Rudolph and Currier (35) (Box 44)
    - German prisoners captures by 93rd at Rogenette (36) (Box 44)
    - Tents of 93rd at Rogenette, general (37) (Box 44)
    - 93rd at Rogenette; Watts, McCone at work; operating, eating; Col. Wilbur; Raggedy Ann: Frew and McCone (38-43) (Box 44)
    - Nurses and Currier of 93rd at Barjols; Roy Rene Hotel, Aix-en-Provence (44-45) (Box 44)
    - 93rd at Rogenette; Maj. Gen. Stayer, Cols. Bernice Wilbur, Ed. J. Tracy, Rudolph, and Currier, Capt. McCone (46-47) (Box 44)
    - Nurses of 93rd ready to leave for Grenoble; Lt. Helen Nelson, dietitian out at farm (48) (Box 44)
    - On road, Rogenette to Die; City of Die; Crest to 11th Evacuation Hospital (49) (Box 44)
    - 11th Evacuation Hospital; milk for Col. Wilbur, Dorothy Sutherland, Bea Parker, and Jackie Martin (50-51) (Box 44)
    - 11th Field Hospital at Crest (52) (Box 44)
    - German Naval Hospital at Les Milles near Aix-en-Provence (53) (Box 44)
    - 27th Fighter Group at Salon, France (54) (Box 44)
    - Rome; Flight between Rome and Lyons (55-56) (Box 44)
    - Lons le Saunier; FFI girl and family (57) (Box 44)
    - Medical Depot at Sellieres, France (58) (Box 44)
    - Air Evacuation holding station at Luxueil (59) (Box 44)
    - Medical depot at Sellieres, France (60) (Box 44)
    - Air evacuation holding station at Luxueil; old couple at Vesoul with English speaking friend; N.P. Hospital; Headquarters, 52nd Medical Battalion eating, Vesoul, French mules (61-64) (Box 44)
    - Train evacuation, Mouchard (65-66) (Box 44)
    - Hospital site and rest center - Rambervillers, Bruyeres (67_ (Box 44)
    - Bruyeres, Bill Batt and dead [German] (68) (Box 44)
    - The front at Belmont with General Patch and General Dahlquist; Battalion Aid boys and Japanese-Americans (69) (Box 44)
    - Church at Epinal; Moselle and town; Headquarters 7th army near Echelon; crossing Moselle between Remiremont and Epinal (70) (Box 44)
    - 51st Evacuation Hospital at Luneville; "Vampire of Southern France" (71) (Box 44)
    - Wedding at the 103rd at Charmes (72) (Box 44)
    - 69th Field Artillery Battalion, Brouvelieures, 131st Field Artillery Battalion (73) (Box 44)
    - With the French before Belfort Luxueil; English hospital with French at Lure (74) (Box 44)
    - Mme. Valon and French before Belfort; General LeClerc at 103rd Evacuation Hospital (75) (Box 44)
    - Promotions at 7th Army Medical Service Headquarters Vesoul (76) (Box 44)
    - Battalion Aid Station in mountains few miles from St. Die; 3rd Division Headquarters at Bruyeres; 15th Regiment 3rd Division Headquarters near Nompatelize; 2000 yards from the front (77-78) (Box 44)
    - People at Nompatelize: scenes near LaSalle (79) (Box 44)
    - At the 10th Field Hospital, 2 miles from the front near Jammenil (80) (Box 44)
    - Clearing station hospital of the 3rd Medical Battalion 3rd Division (81) (Box 44)
    - Paris (82) (Box 44)
    - 93rd at Plombieres (83-84) (Box 44)
    - Skulls from chapel at Cassino (85) (Box 44)
    - U.S. military cemetary at Epinal (86-87) (Box 44)
    - Double exposure of General Patch (88) (Box 44)
    - Col. Ernest Dupuy at Luxueil Press Camp; Lt. James Mar of the 56th Medical Battalion at Epinal; Vittel and on the road there from Epinal (90) (Box 44)
    - Air Evacuation, Naples (91) (Box 44)
    - Air Evacuation, Oran (92) (Box 44)
    - Air Evacuation, arrival at Casa; departure from Casa (93-95) (Box 44)
    - Air evacuation (96), 5 litter shots (Box 44)
    - Air evacuation, lunch between Casa and Azores (97) (Box 44)
    - Air evacuation, the Azores; Azores to Bermauda; hot food at Bermuda (98-100) (Box 44)
    - Air Evacuation, arrival in Miami (101) (Box 44)
    - Extra copy negatives (102) (Box 44)
    - Col. Etter's negatives (Box 44)
    - Mary Shears' (Columbus, Ohio) negatives (Box 44)
    - Inez Kaupman's contacts only (Box 44)
    - M's? contacts only (Box 44)
    - Dorothy McKee's contacts only, 1965 (Box 44)
    - Donald Currier's negatives (Box 44)
    - Chaplain Roley's negatives, 2nd Battalion 157th Infantry Regiment; A.P.O. 45 (Box 44)
    - Col. ? negatives (D-Day, H-Hour, Southern France), 1 35mm roll (Box 44)
    - Contacts (Box 44)
    - Contacts (Box 44)
    - Color slides, 12 containers, 15 each (180 slides) also 70 loose slides (Box 44)
    - War Correspondent A-G; Navy "General Meigs" (L056); 1 miscellaneous; 2 unlabeled (Box 44)
  - WAAC negatives
    - WAACs in Daytona (Box 44)
    - WAACs in training (Box 44)
    - WAAC contacts (Box 44)
    - Color slides, 6 containers, 15 each (90 slides)
      - WAACS in Ft. Des Moines (H634-H637), 2 unlabeled (Box 44)
  - Leica Lantern slide boxes, 3 boxes
    - Family vacation slides, 95 slides (Box 44)
    - Nassau vacation slides, 85 slides (Box 44)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 44)
      "Holtsville School" for Country Gentleman, 1941; University of Maryland Extension Course, 1941; Syracuse University; President Roosevelt Declares War (missing as of 04/24/2009); Sunset, Times-Herald Window; 1937 Train Trip to Hollywood, candids; Jeanette McDonald on Location, Arrowhead Lake; Preston Foster; Anita Louise; Azadia Newman and Scott Cotton, Maine 1940; Al Bennett; Airport; New Jersey; Doris Ahmstrom and ?; "Jean's Portrait"
  - Candids, 35mm rolls
    - Theater, National Theater, unless specified
      - Ethel Barrymore: "Farm of 3 Echoes", 2 rolls (Box 45)
      - John Barrymore and Elaine Barrie: "Our Children" (Box 45)
      - Katherine Cornell, Baltimore: "Flowers of the Forest" (Box 45)
      - Eva La Gallienne (Box 45)
      - Helen Hayes (Box 45)
      - Walter Huston: "Dodsworth", "Knickerbocker Holiday" (Box 45)
      - Gertrude Lawrence (Box 45)
      - Nazimova (Box 45)
      - Cornelia Otis Skinner: "Mansion on the Hudson" (Box 45)
      - Helen Twelvetrees at Olney Theatre (Box 45)
      - Orson Welles and Burgess Meredith in Shakespeare (Box 45)
      - Maude Adams and Stephens College Girls (Box 45)
      - Tallulah Bankhead: "Reflected Glory" (Box 45)
      - Ina Clare: "Dead End", 2 rolls (Box 45)
      - Katherine Cornell: "Wingless Victory", 2 rolls (Box 45)
      - Coward-Lawrence (Box 45)
      - Coward, See also Negatives and contacts: Candids: Musicians and orchestras: Martini-Jepson 22 Nov 1936 (Box 45)
      - Helen Gahagan: "Satars Remain", "St. Helena", 2 rolls (Box 45)
      - Henry Hull: "Plumes in the Dust", 2 rolls (Box 45)
      - Bea Lille, 2 rolls (Box 45)
    - Musicians and orchestras, mostly at Constitution Hall
      - Gershwin and Kindler (Box 45)
      - Myra Hess, pianist (Box 45)
      - Iturbi (Box 45)
      - Hans Kindler conducting, 1935; 3 rolls (Box 45)
      - Josef and Rosina Lhevinne (Box 45)
      - Martini-Jepson, 22 Nov 1936 (Box 45)
      - Philadelphia Orchestra: Ormandy with Rachmaninoff, 1938 (Box 45)
      - Pinsa and Rothberg, 1937 (Box 45)
      - Lili Pons, 17 Jan 1937 (Box 45)
      - Rachmaninoff, 3 rolls (Box 45)
      - Blanca Renard (Box 45)
      - Rosenthal playing (Box 45)
      - Schipa and Kindler (Box 45)
      - Paul Whiteman (Box 45)
      - Harold Bauer (Box 45)
      - Heifetz smiles (Box 45)
      - Hans Kindler conducting (Box 45)
      - Kreisler, December 5, 1939; Constitution Hall, 1938, 3 rolls (Box 45)
      - Menuhin (Box 45)
      - Minneapolis Orchestra: Ormandy (Box 45)
      - Namara-Townsend recital (Box 45)
      - John Powell and Kindler, Constitution Hall (Box 45)
      - Posselt, violinist, and Kindler (Box 45)
      - Stokowski Conducting, 2 rolls (Box 45)
      - Stravinsky (Box 45)
      - Rose Bampton (Box 45)
      - Barbaroli conducting (Box 45)
      - Metropolitan Quartet (Box 45)
      - Nelson Eddy (Box 45)
      - Ormandy conducting (Box 45)
      - Philadelphia Orchestra: Ormandy, Menuhin, 2 Jan 1940 (Box 45)
      - Lili Pons and cello player (Box 45)
      - Rosa Ponselle (Box 45)
      - Arthur Rubenstein, 1930-1937; Jeanette McDonald (Box 45)
      - Stokowski and Philadelphia Orchestra (Box 45)
      - Lawrence Tibbetts (Box 45)
      - Toscanini (Box 45)
    - Miscellaneous theatrical and night clubs
      - Acrobatic dancers, Earle Theater (Box 45)
      - Adler and Draper (Box 45)
      - "Caesar and Cleopatra" (Box 45)
      - Circus, 2 rolls (Box 45)
      - Circus in D.C. (Box 45)
      - Don Cossacks (Box 45)
      - Evelyn Davis (Box 45)
      - "D.C. Melody", 2 rolls, no contacts (Box 45)
      - Sally Evans, 2 rolls (Box 45)
      - Firkusny and Ormandy (Box 45)
      - Nikolas Gafni (Box 45)
      - Dick and Josie Gardiner Band (Box 45)
      - Gayety Theater (Box 45)
      - Percy Grainger (Box 45)
      - Ice Follies, 1940 (Box 45)
      - Maryla Jonas (Box 45)
      - "Kind Lady", Washington Civic (Box 45)
      - Fritz Kreisler (Box 45)
      - Serge Koussevitsky and Boston Symphony (Box 45)
      - Jeanette McDonald (Box 45)
      - James Melton (Box 45)
      - Mrs. Townsend's (missing as of 04/28/2009)
      - Picadilly Club (Box 45)
      - Ricci, violinist (Box 45)
      - Rogennelli and Iturbi (Box 45)
      - Schnabel (Box 45)
      - Snesco and Pressler (Box 45)
      - Tossy Spivakovsky (Box 45)
      - Rise Stevens (Box 45)
      - Szigiti (Box 45)
      - Alec Templeton (Box 45)
      - Troika, 2 rolls (Box 45)
      - Astrid Varny (Box 45)
      - Vronsky and Rabin (Box 45)
      - Sylvia Zaremba (Box 45)
    - Dance
      - Among first candids (Box 45)
      - Ballet Russe, 1935-1940; 6 rolls (Box 45)
      - Dance (Box 45)
      - Dancers at Radio City, See Negatives and contacts: Candids: Events: American Legion parade, New York (Box 45)
      - Evelyn Davis, 1935 (Box 45)
      - Evelyn Davis and Jose Limon (Box 45)
      - Humphrey, Weidman, Limon (Box 45)
      - Jooss Ballet, 2 rolls (Box 45)
      - La Argentina (Box 45)
      - Oriental dancer, Wardman Park Hotel, 2 rolls (Box 45)
      - Shan-Kar, dancer (Box 45)
      - Trudi Schoop, 2 rolls (Box 45)
    - Shows and exhibits
      - Millinery Show, N.Y. Models, 1937; 2 rolls (Box 45)
      - Motor Boat Show, N.Y. (Box 45)
      - N.Y. Horse Show, Madison Square Garden, 1939 (Box 45)
      - Peggy the Pony (Box 45)
      - Shoe Show: Vida Moore and Dorothy Shaffer (Box 45)
      - Sally Victor's Hat Show, N.Y. (Box 45)
    - Conventions
      - Democratic Convention, Philadelphia, 1936; 11 rolls (Box 46)
      - Democratic Convention, Chicago, 1940; 13 rolls (Box 46)
      - Democratic Convention, Chicago, 1940; 2 rolls (Box 46)
      - GOP Convention, Philadelphia, 1940; 13 rolls (Box 46)
    - Washington, DC
      - Annual Message; Roosevelt addresses Congress, 1937; 2 rolls (Box 46)
      - FDR Campaign (Box 46)
      - Inauguration, 1937 (Box 46)
      - Justice Byrnes funeral (Box 46)
      - Opening of Congress, 1935; 1936,; 1937; 3 rolls (Box 46)
      - Roosevelt's birthday ball (2 rolls); Truman at Congress (Box 46)
      - Truman at Press Club Awards dinner, Apr 1948 (Box 46)
    - Events
      - American Legion parade, New York (Box 46)
      - Archibald Curley's installation (Box 46)
      - G A R Parade, 2 rolls (Box 46)
      - World's Fair, Chicago (Box 46)
    - Places
      - Beach (Box 46)
      - Cape May, 4 rolls (Box 46)
      - Ft. Raleigh, N.C. (Box 46)
      - Lighthouse, Turkey Point, MD (Box 46)
      - Nag's Head, 2 rolls (Box 46)
      - Niagara Falls (Box 46)
      - Night air shots, Washington, DC (Box 46)
      - Norfolk - St. Charles Ferry; Atlantic City Beach (Box 46)
      - Shells (Box 46)
      - Sibley Hospital (Box 46)
      - Virginia Beach (Box 46)
      - Winona, 2 rolls (Box 46)
      - At the cottage; mom and pop in tires (Box 46)
      - Dower House, Soldiers' Home, 2 rolls (Box 46)
      - Havana trip; Azadia and Scott's farm in Maine (Box 46)
      - Hollywood, on vacation in Atlantic City, 4 rolls (Box 46)
      - Monticello; Cypress Gardens; University of Virginia (Box 46)
      - Nassau, 5 rolls (Box 46)
      - Plane trip to coast (Box 46)
      - Port Washington; Jackie Martin in hotel room in New York (Box 46)
      - San Simeon, 5 rolls (Box 46)
      - Stephens College, See Negatives and contacts: Candids: Personalities: James Wood; Stephens College
      - Syracuse University (Box 46)
      - University of Maryland, See Negatives and contacts: Candids: Personalities: Curley Byrd; University of Maryland
      - Winona (Box 46)
    - Personalities
      - Boss's judge friend (Box 46)
      - Brisbane funeral (Box 46)
      - Baron Bucovich (Box 46)
      - Curley Byrd; University of Maryland (Box 46)
      - Clement children (Box 46)
      - Bob, Mildred, and Mike Considine (Box 46)
      - Clarence Darrow (Box 46)
      - Maxine Davis; George Dewitt (Box 46)
      - Five women in House of Representatives and Senator Copeland (Box 46)
      - Harrison, Bankhead, Halsey, et al. (Box 46)
      - Hopkins, Garner, Mrs. Garner, and Parliamentarian (Box 46)
      - Helen Koues of Good Housekeeping (Box 46)
      - Sir Wilmot Lewis (Box 46)
      - Lady Lewis (Box 46)
      - Huey Long speaks (Box 46)
      - Alice Longworth (Box 46)
      - Emil Ludwig (Box 46)
      - Mother and dad in Atlantic City (Box 46)
      - Mother and Diddy's birthday party with Nancy (Box 46)
      - Ollie Kate and kids (Box 46)
      - Painting of Jean and Bishops (Box 46)
      - Joe Patterson; Heywood Broun (Box 46)
      - Stanley Reed (Box 46)
      - Justice Vandevanter (Box 46)
      - Victor Watson; Alice Hughes; Doubting Thomas (Box 46)
      - James Wood; Stephens College (Box 46)
      - American Federation of Labor Officials, Washington, DC (Box 46)
      - Charles Harris in jail (Box 46)
      - Mrs. Harrison; wedding shot; Nee Gatyson (Box 46)
      - Ray and Kitty Helgeson wedding (Box 46)
      - Hilles (Box 46)
      - Walter Howey, Arthur Brisbane, Lou Little, Dr. Agna, and Isham Keith (Box 46)
      - Pish and Jerry; Hal Hancock; Garnett at races (Box 46)
      - Senator Rose Long and daughter (Box 46)
      - Clare Boothe Luce (Box 46)
      - National Geographic: Gilbert Grosvenor, Maynard Williams, Cliff Berryman (Box 46)
      - Dr. Richards, Johns Hopkins Hospital (Box 46)
      - Evie Robert and baby at N.Y. Hospital and home; old horse at Ft. Myers (Box 46)
      - George Schein; Mrs. Sol Bloom's house (Box 46)
      - Virgie Stevens at Garfield (Box 46)
      - Three girl flyers; Gypsy Rose Lee at Ritz Carlton (Box 46)
      - Mabel Walker Willebrandt (Box 46)
      - Walter Winchell (Box 46)
      - Bacalova, See Negatives and contacts: Candids: Miscellaneous theatrical and night clubs: Troika
      - Bourke-White, See Negatives and contacts: Parties: White House party practice
      - Eve Currie and Mrs. Harriman, See Negatives and contacts: Assorted negatives 1935-1965: 1940 Press Club stunt party
      - Alice Dowd, See Negatives and contacts: Candids: Shows and exhibits: Millinery Show, N.Y. Models 1937
      - Steve Early, See Negatives and contacts: Candids: Musicians and orchestras: Rose Bampton
      - Senator LaFollette (Box 46)
      - Herbert Hoover, See Negatives and contacts: Sports: Fight
      - Mrs. Hamilton, See Negatives and contacts: Candids: Miscellaneous theatrical and night clubs: Troika
      - Goode Hurje, See Negatives and contacts: Parties: Democratic Women's Club party
      - Jane Mason, See Negatives and contacts: Candids: Musicians and orchestras: Namara-Townsend recital
      - Viola Moore and Dorothy Shaffer, See Negatives and contacts: Candids: Shows and exhibits: Millinery Show, N.Y. Models 1937
      - Pishy, See Negatives and contacts: Editorial and feature coverage: Christmas shopping at Kann's
      - Lillian Rixie at Culpepper, See Negatives and contacts: Candids: Theater: Helen Twelvetrees at Olney Theatre and Negatives and contacts: Sports: Mountain Lake Tennis
      - Tibbetts, See Negatives and contacts: Sports: Preakness
      - Vines, Perry, and Lott, See Negatives and contacts: Sports: Tennis at Maryland University
      - Evie Walker, See Negatives and contacts: Sports: Marlboro
  - Biographical negatives
    - Winona School portraits of Jackie Martin and classmates, Summer 1935; 36 8x10 (Box 47)
    - Jackie Martin's funeral, 19 Dec 1969 (Box 47)
    - Jackie Martin shooting party at Alliance in Paris, 1 4x5 and contacts (Box 47)
    - Jackie Martin portraits, 2 4x5, 1 3x4, various sizes of contacts (Box 47)
    - Jackie Martin portraits, 3 4x5 (Box 47)
    - Jackie Martin at 41 Fauberg Receptions; Man Ray, Steichen, Vigneau, Jackie Martin; Alice Hager, Buck Lanham, Jackie Martin; Countess Katherine d'Juerklow, Jackie Martin; Myrna Loy, Alice Curran, Ivy Preist, Jackie Martin; Preist (Treasurer of US) and Jackie Martin; Nice girl who went to Spain (Bill Cody), Jackie Martin, 6 rollies and contacts (Box 47)
    - Jackie Martin at Gare St. Lazrae in Paris; Suzette Dewey leaves for US; Olga Bologoff and daughter leave for US with Jackie Martin, 3 4x5 (Box 47)
    - Family - Land's End home leave; shots made at bay, June 1952-August 1952; 8 rollies (Box 47)
    - Objects and Creed of the Daughters of the American Revolution, 1 4x5 copy negative (Box 47)
    - Brazilian Award; Alice Hager, Anesia Machado, Ambassador, Jackie Martin, 2 4x5, 1 6.5x2 (Box 47)
    - Family at Diddy's Christmas Day; 2 days after return from ECA, 1949; 8 rollies (Box 47)
    - Jackie Martin: Tankersky and officer, 1 4x5 color positive (Box 47)
    - The "Non-Shift" DeSoto trip: NYC to Hollywood for agency, 1 4x5, 5 3x5 (Box 47)
    - Jackie Martin, Asherville; Adrienne and her boyfriend, 4 2.5x5 (Box 47)
    - Jackie Martin at desk in Paris, 5 avenue Gabriel, 1950; 2 rolies (Box 47)
    - Jackie Martin shoots Evalyn McLean's table at Gold Plate Breakfast, the Carlton, 1 4x5 (Box 47)
    - Jackie Martin shoots Clarence Darrow at Senate hearing, Times-Herald, 35mm strip of 3 (Box 47)
    - Jackie Martin and Duchess of Windsor at Press Club party at Willard Hotel; Esther Tufty, 1 4x5, 1 3x4 (Box 47)
    - Jackie Martin shoots 1940 Democratic Convention in Chicago, 2 4x5 (Box 47)
    - Jackie Martin shoots Churchill in Ottawa and Washington, DC, 5 4x5 copy negatives (Box 47)
    - Family shots: last year at 419 Upshur Street Northwest, 17 4x5 (Box 47)
    - Family shots: early negatives in Washington; Lincoln Park; 419 Upshur - Dad, Mom, Diddy, Philly, Baby Doll, Grandma Martin, 16 4x5, 6 miscellaneous (Box 47)
    - Pop in backyard painting, USSH (Box 47)
    - Outside shots: our house at USSH (Box 47)
    - Unknown (Box 47)
    - Papa and Mama on horseback in Fargo, ND (Box 47)
    - Pop: very early shot (18 years) with his bicycle in North Broddock (Box 47)
    - Trip South to Orlando Mom and Pop took with Lola (Box 47)
    - Corinthia trip, NY; Mama, Papa, Phil, Jerry, Jackie Martin (Box 47)
    - Early days at the bay, rebuilding; Mama, Papa, Diddy, Philly, Jackie Martin (Box 47)
    - Family group shots made by Underwood and Underwood (Box 47)
    - Early shots down at the bay; boat, family, Clements, George and Alma Dewitt, kids (Box 47)
    - Camp Kahlert; Ollie, Baby Doll, the Gang, Jackie Martin; Sherwood Forest (Box 47)
    - The LaSalle; Jackie Martin in Grey Boy (Box 47)
    - Jackie Martin portraits made in Hollywood, 1937 (Box 47)
    - Darkroom at Chicago Sun office, 12th floor of National Press Building, Mar 1941 (Box 47)
    - Jackie Martin at Kent State University (Box 47)
    - Jackie Martin on horseback, USSH (Box 47)
    - General Patch's letter of authorization (Box 47)
    - Jackie Martin at USSH, cherry trees; shots made by Pop, 10 May 1937 (Box 47)
    - Jackie Martin in lab and cellar darkroom, USSH; Steve Kellogg, Laurie Wolcott (Box 47)
    - Jackie Martin; Olga Kahler and snake at Lantana, Florida (Box 47)
    - Jackson's Hole, Wyoming 1934; Chicago World's Fair; Jean, Diddy, Jackie Martin (Box 47)
    - Jackie Martin rests after a shooting session at Fort Des Moines with WAACs (Box 47)
    - Jackie Martin goes off to Fort Des Moines to WAACS, 1942; Jackie Martin, Mama, Papa (Box 47)
    - Martin-Hager return from Brazil; Union Station with families (Box 47)
    - Brazil; Jackie Martin shoots party in evening gown; talking to President Vargas and daughter with group at Palace; long shots of big Brazilian ships launching, See also Negatives and contacts: Brazil 1941-1942 (Box 47)
    - Jackie Martin gets membership to the White House News Photographers Association; Steve Early, Harry Goodwin, Jackie Martin, Tommy Bills, and George Skadding; also color shots, 19 Mar 1942 (Box 47)
    - Jackie Martin at Syracuse University before receiving Arents Award, Jun 1941 (Box 47)
    - Jackie Martin receives Arents Award from Chancellor Graham, 1941 (Box 47)
    - Jackie Martin receives citation from Secretary of War, Robert Patterson, 23 Nov 1946 (Box 47)
    - Jackie Martin takes train at Silver Spring either to Stephens College job or convention (Box 47)
    - Jackie Martin at Delta Gamma House after speech at Ohio State University; with Merry Hull (Box 47)
    - Jackie Martin gets Delta Gamma Rose Award with Betty Holmes (Box 47)
    - Papa's Westinghouse cup and flowers; Papa plays baseball (Box 47)
    - Jackie Martin and Cissy Patterson at Symphony; at Times-Herald homemakers meeting, 1936-1938; 2 4x5 (Box 47)
    - Jackie Martin (10 yrs) winning race in Pittsburgh at Westinghouse Annual Outing at Kennywood Park; Jerry winning race at Kahlert, 2 4x5 (Box 47)
    - Washington sculptor makes bust of Jackie Martin in basketball uniform, 2 4x5 (Box 47)
    - Jackie Martin and Lieutenant Randall Koop at Cora Gables Hospital; Ladies Home Journal job, 2 rollies (Box 47)
    - Jackie Martin with Dorothy Lewis and Julie doing modern dance at Stunt party, 5 3x4 (Box 47)
    - Jackie Martin, Mrs. Esther Tufty, and King George II of Greece, at Willard Hotel, Washington DC; Mom and the king, 1 4x5, 1 3x4 (Box 47)
    - Jackie Martin at Dower House, 1 4x5 (Box 47)
    - Jackie Martin with camera for Times-Herald, 1938 (Box 47)
    - Jackie Martin making speech in New York for professional group; Woodhouse, 3 4x5 (Box 47)
    - Jackie Martin out at Stephens College; Jean, 7 2x4 (Box 47)
    - Jackie Martin, Kathleen McLaughlin ( New York Times), and Harry France (United Press International) (Box 47)
    - Jackie Martin early school shot (Box 47)
    - Jackie Martin with Willa Roberts, editor of Woman's Home Companion; in jeep at War College, 1942 (Box 47)
    - Jackie Martin; Tazewell, Ollie and Gang, David Hert, Ted; Jackie Martin on horseback, 1926; 17 2.5x5 (Box 47)
    - Phil Jr. with Nancy, Pish as little girls at Dr. Davis' Place in Mountains (Box 47)
    - Aunt Diddy and friends; Watermelon party at USSH (Box 47)
    - Mama and Papa, at USSH (Box 47)
    - Dr. Davis; Diddy, Nancy, Pishy, Billy; Phil Jr. and kids (Box 47)
    - Jackie Martin: a "liddle" girl, circa 1907 (Box 47)
    - Mama on porch; Diddy, Baby and Jackie Martin; neighbor girl; 2208 Milligan Avenue, Swissvale, PA, 1915-1917? (Box 47)
    - Jackie Martin and Jerry at luncheon of Mom's club (Box 47)
    - Jackie Martin with President Truman, 30 Apr 1959 (Box 47)
    - Jackie Martin and family at Colonial Beach, 1921 (Box 47)
    - Doc Clements, Jerry and little Jackie Graham (Box 47)
    - Mama and McL.L. (Miss Mary King Sumner); Mama, Papa, Diddy, and McL.L.; group shot at USSH (Box 47)
    - Penny Martin at Mount Vernon and earlier shots at USSH; Mama, Papa, Bobbie, and Minny (Box 47)
    - Ginnie Wallace Bright, Adrienne, Jackie Martin; USSH (Box 47)
    - Mama takes her first plane trip (Box 47)
    - Mom's passport picture (Box 47)
    - Mom, Jerry, Jackie Martin at Mom's club with group; Bobbie and Minnie Boyd (Box 47)
    - Family at birthday party (Box 47)
    - Mama, Papa, Diddy, Jean; off to Cuba (Box 47)
    - Mama, her sister Jane Eisenbeis, and her daughter, Lillian at USSH (Box 47)